So it finally happened. I got no people
in for a show, which I think is the
first time this has happened in three
years of doing the fringe. But it
is kind of like the theatre gods'
way, and the theatre is for gods, I
think. I think that's the way the
word comes from. It is the theatre
gods way of telling me that I need
to sort out my publicity machine.
I'm the publicity machine and I'm not
sorted out so the thing that I did
was I did the entire show anyway I
didn't stop for the writing breaks
but I just talked about all the
things beginning with S and then I
heckle myself at the
end which is demented
but the thing is that
that kind of that video
I can post that tonight
I will post that tonight
I'm only going to kind of treat
myself to one thing either a beer or
some fish and chips I'm not sure
which one of those I'm going to go for
but I'm going to treat myself to
one of those things either a beer or
some fish or chips
to celebrate the fact that I've done
a twelve date show run so I wrote
produced and directed for some value
of all of those things as they say
in computer language
the show this year You Can Write a Book
and I know from previous
experience that I'm talking about
these things is part of the way that I
get them to actually come into being
and turn out as real books in the
future.
So I'm very positive about it and I'm
going to stop there because I want
this to be a short.